酒席承办人给我十二道开胃菜清单 我得将选择范围缩小到六道
The caterer sent me this list of 12 appetizers. I have to narrow it to six.
食物问题? 交给我吧
Food? Oh, give me.
莫妮卡跟你们提过我们结婚时要请摇摆国王来演唱吗?
Did Monica mention we're trying to get The Swing Kings to play the wedding?
你喜欢摇摆音乐?
You're into swing music?
我以前会跑遍全城听乐团演奏
I used to go all over town listening to bands.
-钱德 -对，是GAP的广告词（年轻人服装品牌）
- Chandler? - Gap commercial.
-你打电话订下他们了吗? -我会打的
- Did you book them? Did you call? - I will.
-你要我打吗? -我会打的 你只需要做好你的工作
- You want me to call? - I'll do it. You stick to your job.
-你的工作是什么? -别碍事
- What is your job? - Staying out of the way.
这是不可能的，你为什么不挑清单上的十五道开胃菜
This is impossible. Why don't you just pick all 15.
-只有十二道而己 -对，我加了三道
- There were only 12. - Oh, yeah, I added three.
什么是花生酱手指?
What are peanut-butter fingers?
Friends S07E17 廉价的婚纱
The One With the Cheap Wedding Dress
你好
Well, hello.
她好可爱
She's cute.
我们该跟她说话吗?
Should we go try to talk to her?
当然，订婚后跟美女说话我再也不会紧张
Sure. Being engaged, I'm not nervous talking to pretty girls anymore.
你们能过来帮帮我吗?
Could you guys help me?
我来帮你搬那个
Yeah, let me get that for you.
-它真的很重 -没问题
- It's really heavy. - I got it.
嗨，我是罗斯，他是我朋友钱德
So hi, I'm Ross, and this is my friend Chandler.
我是克丽丝汀
I'm Kristen.
克丽丝汀，嗨，你刚搬来吗?
Kristen, hi. Are you new to the area?
如果你刚搬来这里我可以带你四处参观一下
Because if you are, I'd love to show you around sometime.
事实上，我只从四条街外搬来这里而已
I actually just moved from four blocks over.
但这里好像另一个世界
But this block is like another world.
事实上这个地区的历史非常有趣
Actually, it does have a very interesting history.
这条街是纽约第一条有下水道系统的街道
This street is the first in the city to have an underground sewer system.
之前污水跟废弃物…
Before that, sewage and waste...
会直接流到街上
...would just flow right down the street.
有时到了脚踝
Sometimes ankle-deep.
说得好
Smooth.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
搬完家你一定会肚子饿 你想跟我一起去吃晚餐吗
You're gonna be starving after moving. What do you say I take you to dinner?
-我很乐意 -太棒了
- I'd like that. - Great.
我帮你把箱子搬上去
Let me take this up.
-你先请-不，你先请
- After you. - Oh, no. After you.
我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
是我疯了还是这真的很配?
Am I crazy, or does this totally go?
我的天啊! 你看起来好漂亮!
Oh, my God! You look so beautiful!
谢谢你，瑞秋，但看看莫妮卡
Thank you, Rachel. But look at Monica!
就是它，就是这件
This is it. Yeah, this is the one.
我不敢相信我找到它了
I can't believe I found it.
你看起来好漂亮 如果我认识你，我会哭的
Wow, you look so beautiful. If I knew you, I'd cry.
我是莫妮卡盖勒，幸福的新娘
I'm Monica Geller. Ball like a baby.
我是梅根巴利
I'm Megan Bailey.
-你找到婚纱了吗? -这些婚纱都很漂亮…
- Have you found your dress? - These dresses are amazing...
-但我买不起 -我也是
...but I couldn't afford one. - I can't either.
我只是来这里找婚纱 然后我会到克莱门婚纱店买
I'm here to figure out which one I want, then I'll get it at Kleinmars.
他们在大减价
They're having a huge sale.
-谢谢你的情报 -你什么时候结婚?
- Thanks for the tip. - When are you getting married?
-我没有要结婚，我只是想试穿婚纱 -我也会那么做
- I'm not. I just like to try these on. - I do the same thing.
我只是在开玩笑，我的婚期是七月二十五日
I'm just kidding. I'm getting married July 25.
我也只是在开玩笑
I'm just kidding too.
我要在十二月结婚
I'm getting married in December.
-你什么时候结婚? -五月十五日
- When are you getting married? - May 15.
已经很接近了，你请谁拍照?
It's getting close. Who's your photographer?
-杰佛瑞 -我们跟他谈过
- Jeffrey. - We met with him.
-他拿裸体婚纱照给你们看了吗？-那个伴郎吗? 哇!
- Did he show you nude wedding photos? - The best man? Wow!
我知道，我差点取消了婚礼
I know. I almost called off my wedding.
-你请了哪个乐团? -我未婚夫想请摇摆国王
- Who's your band? - My fiance wants The Swing Kings.
你真幸运，我未婚夫想请“动物尸体重金属乐团”
You're lucky. My fiance wants the heavy metal band, Carcass.
是C开头的还是K开头的? 那不重要，他们都很棒!（Karcass也是知名乐队）
Is that spelled with a C or a K? It doesn't matter, they're both great!
别在这里买婚纱
Oh, don't buy that here.
现在你知道你喜欢哪一件 到克莱门婚纱店买
Now that you know what you want, go to Kleinmars.
这里的婚纱大贵了
This place is so overpriced.
我是这的老板
I own this store.
这件婚纱有别的颜色吗? 还是…?
So does this come in another color, or...?
嗨，你要搬进来还是搬走?
Hi. You moving in or moving out?
-我要搬进来 -需要我帮忙吗?
- Moving in. - Can I give you a hand?
好吧，但是你得小心一点 来帮我的那个人因为背痛先走了
Okay, but be careful. Guy who was helping me had to leave because he hurt his back.
-他是你男朋友? -不是
- Boyfriend? - No.
我是乔伊
I'm Joey.
我是克丽丝汀
Kristen.
你的名字真好听
What a beautiful name.
你说你叫什么?
What is it again?
克丽丝汀
Kristen.
-你住在附近? -我就住在那边
- You live around here? - Right down there.
我得提供你一些资讯
Let me give you a little tip.
别在那个楼梯上睡觉 醒过来时你的鞋子可能已经被偷了
Don't take a nap on this stoop. You could wake up with your shoes gone.
我会记住的
I'll remember that.
听着，今晚你要跟我一起吃饭吗?
Listen, would you like to have dinner with me tonight?
今晚我有约了，明天可以吗?
I have plans tonight. How about tomorrow?
听起来不错，这个要搬到哪里?
Sounds great. Well, where does this go?
你看起来很壮，把它交给我 你去帮我搬箱子吧
You look strong. Why don't I take that, and you grab one of the boxes.
书  靠垫
我来搬这个
Yeah, I'll get this one.
这里就是布鲁克林?(纽约西南部的工业区)
So this is Brooklyn?
听着，通常每件婚纱一个尺寸只有一件
Listen up. There's usually only one dress in each size.
他们一开门，马上冲进去
So when they open those doors, fan out.
这就是你们的目标，记住它
This is what you're looking for. Memorize it.
找到婚纱后就吹哨子，好吗?
When you locate the dress, blow on these, all right?
用力吹三声，一听到哨音后马上跑过来
Three sharp blasts. When you hear it, come running.
他来了!
Here he comes!
-他们在推我! -别那么孩子气!
- They're pushing! - Don't be a baby!
-别挡路! -我们冲吧!
- Out of the way! - Let's go!
瑞秋? 快一点!
Rachel?! Come on!
不，不是
No, not it. Not it. Not it.
别推我
Don't crowd me.
就是它! 就是这件婚纱! 太完美了!
This is it! This is the dress! It's perfect!
对不起，这件是我的
I'm sorry, this one's taken!
-梅根! -莫妮卡!
- Megan! - Monica!
-你来了! -是的!
- You came! - Yeah!
-这是我的婚纱! -不!
- This is my dress! - No!
-没错，它就是，你看到我试穿它 -现在你会看到我买下它
- Yes it is. You saw me wearing it. - And now you'll see me buying it.
你这个怪胎
You freak!
如果没有我你根本不知道这个地方
You wouldn't even know about this place without me.
-听着，你不会想跟我争 -或许我想，我是很凶的
- Look, you don't want to fight me.- Maybe I do. I'm pretty feisty!
-我来了…-嘿!
- I'm coming! I'm coming! - Hey!
好了! 嘿? 我该怎么办?
Okay! Hey? Oh, what do I do?!
你在做什么? 你找到婚纱了吗?
What are you doing? Did you find the dress?
你找到婚纱了吗?
Did you find the dress?
不，快救我出去，这些女人都疯了
No. Get me out of here. These shoppers are crazy.
-我们得去找莫妮卡，-你得抓住我的手  -上帝啊
- We've gotta get Monica. - You gotta hold my hand! -Oh my god
借过…
Excuse me! Excuse me!
快走…
Go! Go! Go!
罗斯，那晚你跟她约会还顺利吧?
So, Ross, how was your date the other night?
你跟她提过只要一冲马桶 魔法之旅就开始了吗?
Did you tell her about the magical ride that starts with every flush?
尽管笑吧，但说她想再跟我约会
Laugh all you want, but she said she'd like to go out again.
事实上，我正要打电话给她
In fact, I'll go call her right now.
我会确定并告诉她 我朋友钱德说…
And I'll make sure and tell her my friend Chandler says...
抱歉昨晚我失约了，但我有个约会
Sorry I didn't stop by last night, but I had a date.
你说你凌晨一点要过来 就算你没来，也没有关系
When it's 1:00 in the morning and you don't come by, that's okay.
我跟一个辣妹约会，她刚刚搬到对街
It was with this really hot girl who just moved in right across the street.
-真的吗? 她住在对街? -对
- Really? Right across the street? - Yeah.
-你什么时候认识她的? -两天前
- When did you meet her? - Two days ago.
太棒了!
Excellent!
罗斯也认识了一个女孩
You know, Ross met somebody too.
-嘿 -怎么样?
- Hey. - How'd it go?
太棒了，我们星期六要再出去玩
Great. We're going out again Saturday.
但我刚刚发现她也在跟别人约会
But I just found out she's also seeing some other guy.
真的吗?
Really?
乔伊，如果你是罗斯你会怎么做?
Joe, what would you do if you were in Ross' situation?
我跟他差不多 跟我约会的女孩也在跟别人约会
I sort of am. I'm dating this girl who's also seeing another guy.
但我一点都不担心
But I'm not worried about it.
你不必担心，我不想当你的竞争者
You shouldn't be. I wouldn't want to be the guy who's up against you.
那个混蛋一定会输的
I mean, that doofus is going to lose.
这真的太有趣了
So this is nice.
真希望我能留下来，相信我
I wish I didn't have to go. Believe me.
但我得走了
But I have to.
对了，跟你们约会的女孩叫什么名字?
By the way, what's the name of the girl you're dating?
-克丽丝汀莱夫 -再见
- Kristen Leigh. - Bye.
很明显地，我们之中只有一个人能继续跟她约会
Well, obviously only one of us can keep dating her.
没错，我们该怎么决定?
Obviously. So how do we decide?
好了，我们得客观地来解决这件事
Well, now, let's look at this objectively.
我想我该跟她约会
I think I should date her.
或是我该跟她约会
Or I'm the one who dates her.
那真的很有趣，但是听好了 我跟她约会
That's interesting. But check this out. I date her.
好吧，但是换个角度来说…
Okay, but to go in another direction...
好吧，我们是谈不出结论来的
Okay. This can go on for a while.
-那么我们该点些吃的 -不，乔伊
- We should order some food, then. - No, Joey.
听着，我们为什么不让她来决定?
Look, why don't we just let her decide, okay?
我们都再跟她约会一次
We'll each go out with her one more time.
看看她比较喜欢谁
And we'll see who she likes best.
听起来很公平
That sounds fair.
或许我会带她到新开的法国餐厅吃饭
Maybe I'll take her to that new French restaurant.
等一下，我们得对约会费用设下限制
Wait a second. We have to set a spending limit on the date.
我没有钱带她到高级餐厅吃饭
I don't have the money to take her to a fancy place like that.
抱歉，那是我的约会方式
Well, sorry. That's what I do on dates.
我猜我得用我的约会方式
Well, I guess I'll just have to do what I do on dates.
-我们来决定费用上限 -好
- So let's decide on a spending limit. - Yeah.
大概是…
And a slice...
六块钱?
...$6?
-我想是一百块 -好吧
- I was thinking more like 100. - Okay.
你能借给我九十四块吗?
Can I borrow $94?
我知道，你能帮我拿张面纸吗?
I know. Can you hand me a tissue?
你没有健怡可乐了
You're out of Diet Coke.
喂?
Hello?
什么? 你什么?
What? You what?
你给我听好了，小姐!
You listen here, missy!
是梅根打来的，她订下了摇摆国王 日期是我们结婚的那一天
That was Megan. She booked The Swing Kings on the day of our wedding...
还说如果我不把婚纱让给她，我就没有乐团
...and said I couldn't have them back unless I gave her the dress!
那么 动物尸体乐团有空了?
Does that mean Carcass is available?
我该怎么办? 我好喜欢那件婚纱!
What am I gonna do? That's the dress! That is the dress!
钱德喜欢那个乐团，我该怎么办?
Chandler wants the band. What do I do?
-想办法说服他放弃，-我该怎么办?
- Figure out a way to talk him out of it. - How?
你的卫生纸用完了
You're out of toilet paper!
我要来祝你约会顺利
I wanted to wish you good luck on your date.
-谢谢 -你们约几点?
- Thanks. - What time are you meeting?
我们在葛兰梅西毕斯多餐厅订了八点的位子
We have 8:00 reservations at Grand Merci Bistro.
时间只剩下二十分钟 你最好快去换衣服
That's in 20 minutes. You'd better get dressed.
-我已经换好衣服了，-太好了
- I am dressed. - Oh, well, good.
对我来说
For me.
这是什么? 你在敷脸?
What's this? Did you give yourself a facial?
我的T字部位是油性的
I have an oily T-zone.
好吧，兄弟
Okay, dude.
-你送克丽丝汀花? -没错
- You sent Kristen flowers?- That's right.
你花了一百块，你把钱花光了，你输了!
You spent $ 100. That's the limit. You're screwed!
我在约会前送她花，所以技术上来说…
I sent the flowers before the actual date, so technically...
我没有犯规
...I didn't break any rules.
谢谢你来看我
Thanks for stopping by, though.
-你真的要那么玩? -我也可以犯规
That's the way it's gonna be? I can break the rules too.
-你打算怎么办 -我不知道
- What are you gonna do? - I don't know.
-为什么我一点都不讶异 -我不会放过你的
- Why am I not surprised? - Not gonna let you get away with this.
-我想你没有太多选择 -我们走着瞧
- I don't think you have much choice. - We'll see!
嘿! 只要薄薄地敷一层就好?
Hey! So, just a light layer?
对，只要敷这里跟这里
Yeah, just here and there.
乔伊又把肉酱滴在扶手上了
Joey got meat sauce on the banister again.
摇摆音乐太落伍了
Swing music is so out.
他得在这房间里才可以听的到
He's gotta be in the room for that to work.
你们到底在说什么?
What are you guys talking about?
我们在谈摇摆国王…
We're talking about The Swing Kings...
讨论到底该不该请他们来
...and wondering whether they're the right way to go.
有一次我去参加请摇摆乐团来表演的婚礼
I went to a wedding once where they had swing music...
两个月后他们就离婚了
...and two months later, the couple divorced.
我不是说这其中有什么关系…
I'm not saying there's any connection here...
但他们的确告诉我那是他们离婚的原因
...but they did tell me that's why they got divorced.
但我喜欢摇摆音乐!
But I love swing music!
但摇摆国王?
But The Swing Kings?
他们烂到有人听他们的演唱会死掉 他们就是不想活了
They suck so much that people die at their concerts. They just stop living.
我只知道莫妮卡跟我去看他们演唱时非常开心
All I know is that when Monica and I went to see them, we had fun.
事实上还有一个原因
And there's another reason.
-是什么原因? -我不想说
- Well, what is the other reason? - I don't want to say.
你非说不可，或许它很蠢
Well, you have to because maybe it's stupid.
莫妮卡跟我随着他们的音乐起舞…
It's just, while Monica and I were dancing to them...
我第一次知道…
...it was the first time I knew that...
你就是我想一辈子共舞的女人
...you were the woman that I wanted to dance all my dances with.
哦，烂透了
Oh, crap.
-我们的桌子马上就准备好 -太棒了
- Our table will be ready in a few minutes. - Oh, great.
-你的背好一点了吗? -没事了
- Is your back feeling better? - Yeah, that's fine.
我猜肌肉越多…
I guess the more muscles you have...
就越可能抽筋
...the more they can spasm out of control.
-克丽丝汀? -乔伊!
- Kristen? - Joey!
-你来这里做什么? -我喜欢这个地方
- What are you doing here? - I like this place.
技术上来说，我没有犯规，所以…
And technically, I'm not breaking any rules, so...
罗斯，他是乔伊，乔伊，罗斯
Well, Ross, this is Joey. Joey, Ross.
-嗨 -嗨，很高兴能认识你
- Hi. - Hi. It's nice to meet you.
我以前有个朋友叫乔伊
I used to have a friend named Joey.
但他不再是我朋友
I don't anymore.
我们的桌子马上就会准备好
Our table will be ready in a couple minutes.
当然，我想跟你们一起等! 谢谢!
Sure, I would love to wait with you guys! Thanks!
乔伊，你看起来好眼熟
So, Joey, you look familiar.
你上过电视吗?
Are you on TV or something?
乔伊不喜欢提这件事…
Joey doesn't like to talk about it...
但他主演过《我们的日子》
...but he's one of the stars of Days of Our Lives.
没错，你是演女人吗?
That's right. Don't you play a woman?
那是被困在男人身体里的女人
A woman in a man's body.
那可好多了
Much better.
真有趣，因为我也觉得你很眼熟
It's funny, because you look familiar to me too.
你结过婚吗?
Have you ever been married?
我结过婚
Yes, I have.
事实上，前几天…
In fact, just the other day...
克丽丝汀跟我还谈到我结过婚，有个儿子
...Kris and I were talking about how I've been married and how I have a son.
-小艾力克 -没错，等一下，不，是班
- Little Eric. - That's right. Wait. No, Ben.
你只结过一次婚吗?
So you've just been married the one time, then?
-嗯…-你结过两次婚?
- Well... - You've been married twice?
对，那个…
Yes. And...
之后又结了一次
...another time after that.
天啊，我饿了
Boy, I'm getting hungry.
你曾经在约会时饿到…
Have you ever been so hungry on a date...
趁女伴去上洗手间偷吃掉她的食物吗?
...that when the girl goes to the bathroom, you eat her food?
你说是服务生吃掉了我的蟹饼
You said the waiter ate my crab cake.
罗斯，你的第一段婚姻为什么会结束?
So, Ross, now why did that first marriage break up?
因为你前妻是异性恋或因为她是同性恋?
Was it because the woman was straight or because she was a lesbian?
-你们认识吗? -不认识
- Do you two know each other? - No.
只是罗斯看起来像是会跟有同性恋倾向的女人．
Just seems like Ross is the kind of guy who'd marry a woman...
结婚后，逼得她非得出轨的男人
...on the verge of being a lesbian and then push her over the edge.
等一下，你拍过性病海报吧?
Wait a minute! Were you on a poster for gonorrhea?
你跟猴子同床共枕过吧?
Have you ever slept in the same bed with a monkey?
别把马修扯进来!
You leave Marcel out of this!
好吧，你曾经被自己的皮裤卡住了?
Fine! You ever gotten stuck in a pair of your own leather pants?
你曾经把自己锁在电视柜里吗？ 性病小子
Have you ever locked yourself in a TV cabinet, VD-boy?
猴子爱人!
Monkey-lover!
你觉得她是什么时候离开的?
Where do you think we lost her?
可能是性病那一段吧
Probably around gonorrhea.
盖勒，两人桌?
Geller, table of two?
-你饿吗? -出去喝杯啤酒?
- You hungry? - Does a bear shit in the woods?
-甜心，我回来了! -别进来!
- Hi, honey, I'm home! - Don't come in here!
怎么了? 你的另一个男朋友在里面?
Why, do you have another boyfriend in there?
不，我们只会在他家胡搞
No. We only mess around at his place.
虽然是我开的头 但我开始担心了，你能出来吗
I started it, but now it's scaring me, so could you come out here, please?
不行，我正穿着婚纱
No, I'm wearing a wedding dress.
你买到婚纱了?
You got a wedding dress?
-对，但我要把它退回去 -那么我为什么不能看到它
- Yeah, but I'm not keeping it. - Then why can't I see it?
我猜应该可以
Oh. I guess you can.
但我得把它退回去 所以你绝不能喜欢它
But I have to return it, so you can't like it.
好吧，我发誓我会恨它
Okay, I promise. I'll hate it.
哇，你看起来好可怕
Wow. You look hideous.
真的吗?
Really?
那是我看过最丑的婚纱
Yeah. That's like the most ugliest dress I've ever seen.
你为什么要把它退回去?
Why do you have to return it?
因为它真的不合适
Because it doesn't really fit.
还有，我订了摇摆国王
Oh, by the way, I booked The Swing Kings.
那真的是太棒了，谢谢
Oh, that's great. Thanks.
但那件婚纱可怕极了
But that dress is terrible.
-它让我想把它从你身上扯下来 -好吧
- It makes me want to rip it off you. - Okay.
但你不可以把它弄破
But you can't rip it.
或许弄破一点也没关系
Well, maybe a little.
你们想看看婚礼上演唱歌曲的清单吗?
Guys, you want to look at the song list for the wedding?
伙计们?
Guys?
我还以为你会去一整天
I thought you were gonna be gone all day.
好吧，发生了什么事?
All right, what's going on?
对不起，或许我应该让你们这些小女生独处一下
I'm sorry. I should probably leave you girls alone.
尽管笑吧，但十分钟后我们会有年轻好看的皮肤
Laugh all you want, but in 10 minutes, we'll have younger-looking skin.
她该敷一下脸的…
You know, she could use a little...
好球! 太帅了!
Oh, nice shot! Yeah!